From geek to chic in one week? Her afterlife depends on it!
Teen Spirit is a drama, fantasy, comedy film directed by Gil Junger.
Amber, a mean popular girl who gets electrocuted and dies, is not allowed to enter into heaven unless she helps
the least popular girl in school become Prom Queen within a week, but things do not go as planned.
Amber, played by Cassie Scerbo.
Lisa, played by Lindsey Shaw.
Nick, played by Chris Zylka.
Vesper, played by Rhoda Griffis.
Selena, played by Katie Sarife.
Raj Kukuri, played by Paras Patel.
Teen Spirit is an American teen comedy film, directed by Gil
Junger and starring Cassie Scerbo and Lindsey Shaw.
In United States, Teen Spirit was premiered on ABC Family on August 7,
2011, but in South America the film had a theatrical release.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.